# **Robert Wagner** | Sr. Technical Support

Salt Lake City, UT

rob.wagnerusa@protonmail.com | LinkedIn Profile | Portfolio Website | C. 385.495.4015

## **Professional Summary**

**About Me** | Dynamic background in Communications, Sales & Marketing, Education, and Technical Support with 20+ years of combined professional experience.

**Why Product/Applications Support** | With a broad professional background, a passion for solving problems and helping both my team and our customers succeed, I'm excited to continue my career in SaaS Product and Applications Support!

## **Skills & Experience**

- **Technical Writing/Case Notes** | Well-documented discovery and solutions processes, including screenshots where applicable. Leadership has praised me on my technical documentation
- Communications | Recognized by leadership as an expert communicator, especially written where my case notes were regularly referenced to solve similar complex issues Software |
  Microsoft Outlook, Word, Excel, Teams, CRM, Salesforce, GoToAssist, ServicePro
- **Special Projects** | Leadership asked me to upgrade our fillable Annual Review PDF to a more dynamic and comprehensive online Form, which benefited the entire company for years!
- Operating Systems | Microsoft Windows 7-11, Server 2008-2022, also SQL Server, SSMS
- Languages | HTML, XML, RegEx, CSS, and JavaScript
- **Web Applications** | Setup, discovery and implementation of IIS Web Applications, including working with PHP Manager, Web-based Forms, and Workflows.

## **Employment**

**Applications Support Engineer II** | MVi - Millennial Vision, Inc.

2018 - 2024

MVi/CDi provides SaaS Solutions for Financial Institutions and Municipalities in Electronic Content Management systems, including hardware and software deployment, configuration, and support.

- **Productivity** | Completed 30+ complex contracts in 2023 in addition to ticket escalation load
- Case Management | Taking on lengthy cases to reduce overall response time for frontline
- IT Project Management | Regularly coordinate with internal/external resources on 10+ projects
- On-site Implementations | Travel to customer locations and deploy both SaaS Software,
   Technical Hardware, and ran configurations and training as part of the implementations process

- **Productivity** | Fast-paced, solutions-driven, objectives achieved. Sometimes solving 100+ tickets/month where it was common for team members to achieve between 40-60
- **UX Design** | Also served as a local website resource, responsible for adding documents, and managing updates/menus with UX of company website

#### **Recruiting Manager** | Robert Half

2017

Robert Half provides talent sourcing services for Finance and Accounting roles, as well as Technical and other business process roles.

#### **Assistant Branch Manager** Utah First Federal Credit Union

2016-2017

- Design | Designed a branch-specific marketing slick, and used it to prospect local dealerships
- Sales | Added 3 new dealer partners to the branch the same week and began taking applications
- **Team building** | Reduced branch turnover from 75% to 25% by analyzing the team's motivations/interests, providing regular branch snacks (on my own dime, but worth it), as well as a positive, upbeat attitude to help keep the team happy and engaged

#### **Field Admissions Representative** | Universal Technical Institute, Inc.

2012 - 2015

Universal Tech. provides technical career training for Automotive, Diesel, and motorsports industries.

- **Public Relations** | Conducted 400+ interviews with students and their families to discuss their education & career path, and plan a course to help them achieve it
- Public Speaking | Delivered 1,000's of career planning presentations in High Schools
- **Productivity** | Generated over \$1,000,000 in successful starts my 2<sup>nd</sup> and 3<sup>rd</sup> years each.
- **B2B and Education industry relations** | Went from 15 active accounts to over 50 active accounts by conducting consistent follow up, professionalism, and professional relationship building.

#### **Member Consultant** | Boeing Employees Credit Union (BECU)

2006 - 2012

- **CU Experience** | 6+ years delivering world-class member service in full-suite financial products.
- Forecasting/Marketing | BECU needed to gain a base of younger members for future growth. I coordinated and visited high schools to provide financial literacy training for students, which resulted in multiple new member applications from the younger generation

Click to view <u>full employment</u> history

### **Education**

BS - Web Design & Development | BYU